<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<system>3ds</system>
		<software>ARRM</software>
		<web>http://jujuvincebros.fr/wiki/arrm/doku.php</web>
	</provider>
	<game id="12043">
		<path>./Animal Crossing - Happy Home Designer (USA)(En,Fr) Decrypted.3ds</path>
		<name>請按一下這裡</name>
		<sortname>05 =-  Animal Crossing - Happy Home Designer (USA)(En,Fr) Decrypted</sortname>
		<desc>為所有你最喜歡的《動物之森》村民設計家園，展示你的風格！發揮您的創造力，為新老朋友設計從內到外的完美房屋。使用新的 amiibo 卡，您可以召喚您最喜歡的村民進入遊戲。
特點：
為動物村民設計數百個房屋的內部和外部
為學校、醫院和其他公共設施留下您的裝飾風格
收集並連接 - 收集並分享您最喜歡的 amiibo 卡...</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20150925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<family>Animal Crossing</family>
		<region>eu</region>
		<lang>fr,en</lang>
		<image>./images/Animal Crossing - Happy Home Designer (USA)(En,Fr) Decrypted-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Animal Crossing - Happy Home Designer (USA)(En,Fr) Decrypted-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Animal Crossing - Happy Home Designer (USA)(En,Fr) Decrypted-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11971">
		<path>./Hello Kitty Happy Happy Family (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>請按一下這裡</name>
		<sortname>36 =-  Hello Kitty Happy Happy Family (Europe)</sortname>
		<desc>與凱蒂和她的全家人一起玩耍。
通過 25 個有趣的研討會，邊學習邊享受樂趣。
為凱蒂和咪咪收集數百張圖像和偽裝！</desc>
		<developer>Bigben Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Bigben Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Various</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>eu</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Hello Kitty Happy Happy Family (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hello Kitty Happy Happy Family (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Hello Kitty Happy Happy Family (Europe)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="176339">
		<path>./Poochy &amp; Yoshi's Woolly World (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>請按一下這裡</name>
		<sortname>62 =-  Poochy &amp; Yoshi's Woolly World (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>當您引導 Yarn Yoshi 或 Yarn Poochy 通過巧妙的橫向捲軸關卡時，探索充滿創意的手工藝世界。解開秘密，將紗線扔到編織平台上，並通過羊毛變形來增強力量。Wii U 版本的所有關卡均加入了由 Poochy 主演的新關卡以及更多 Nintendo 3DS 獨有功能！
在新的 Poochy 關卡中，這是一次瘋狂的珠子衝刺：躲避樹樁，衝破雪路，追逐拉基圖，並挖掘隱藏的道路和物品。嗅出秘密...</desc>
		<developer>Good-Feel</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Poochy &amp; Yoshi's Woolly World (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Poochy &amp; Yoshi's Woolly World (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Poochy &amp; Yoshi's Woolly World (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11060">
		<path>./Professor Layton and the Miracle Mask (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>請按一下這裡</name>
		<sortname>63 =-  Professor Layton and the Miracle Mask (Europe)</sortname>
		<desc>雷頓教授和盧克前往奇蹟小鎮蒙多爾尋找奇蹟面具。面具有能力實現佩戴者的願望。雷頓和盧克到達小鎮後發現為時已晚，一名神秘男子正在利用面具的力量將人們變成石頭。雷頓和盧克的任務是解開蒙多爾之謎和奇蹟面具。
《雷頓教授》系列的第五款遊戲更多地利用物理按鈕控制來解決謎題……</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20121028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>eu</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Professor Layton and the Miracle Mask (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Professor Layton and the Miracle Mask (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Professor Layton and the Miracle Mask (Europe)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11099">
		<path>./Project X Zone (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>請按一下這裡</name>
		<sortname>64 =-  Project X Zone (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>Project X Zone 由 Banpresto 和 Monolith Soft 開發，擁有來自日本最多產的三個視頻遊戲公司的 29 個歷史遊戲系列的 50 多個角色。在 Project X Zone 中，玩家將使用兩個角色組成的團隊（稱為“配對單位”）來探索遊戲中的世界。稱為單人單位的附加角色可以與配對單位組合，以協助單人攻擊的戰鬥，並增強玩家可以執行的攻擊。在整個比賽過程中，ep...</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20121011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Monolith Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Project X Zone (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Project X Zone (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Project X Zone (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="12051">
		<path>./Project X Zone 2 (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>請按一下這裡</name>
		<sortname>65 =-  Project X Zone 2 (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>在原創跨界 RPG 冒險的續集中，來自日本最多產的視頻遊戲發行商的傳奇人物齊聚一堂，創造了有史以來最大的混搭策略遊戲！Project X Zone 2 讓玩家有機會扮演眾多系列中他們最喜歡的角色，並組建來自經典和當前系列的角色團隊，並通過戰略回合製戰鬥與敵人交戰。</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20160216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Project X Zone 2 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Project X Zone 2 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Project X Zone 2 (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="176356">
		<path>./Puzzler World 2012 3D (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>請按一下這裡</name>
		<sortname>66 =-  Puzzler World 2012 3D (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>借助 Puzzler World 2012 3D，玩家可以在個人獎杯櫃中收集獎杯作為技能證明，收集提示標記以幫助解決棘手的線索和謎題，並教遊戲使用手寫識別功能記住單個字母和數字。通過使用新模式解鎖獎勵遊戲來增加更多的多樣性和更多的樂趣。通過挑戰模式進行額外的獎勵遊戲，例如絞刑吏、連環信、失踪的碎片等等。如需額外挑戰，請解鎖大師模式謎題......</desc>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<md5>4c4226f730f616308fcc7852cfebbceb</md5>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Puzzler World 2012 3D (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Puzzler World 2012 3D (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Puzzler World 2012 3D (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="176357">
		<path>./Puzzler World 2013 (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>請按一下這裡</name>
		<sortname>67 =-  Puzzler World 2013 (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>Puzzler World 2013 包含 1,200 多個腦筋急轉彎謎題，並推出了 Maze-a-Pix、Number Jig 和 Loko 等新遊戲。

Puzzler World 2013 進一步推進了大師模式，推出了新的、更艱鉅的挑戰，玩家可以解鎖並測試自己。</desc>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<md5>15859a610351d00f2191ef58537d2ca7</md5>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Puzzler World 2013 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Puzzler World 2013 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Puzzler World 2013 (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="176358">
		<path>./Rabbids - Travel in Time 3D (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>請按一下這裡</name>
		<sortname>68 =-  Rabbids - Travel in Time 3D (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>兔子們瘋了，這一次他們有一個萬無一失的計劃：回到過去併入侵人類歷史！與古怪的瘋兔一起沉浸在過去，重溫歷史上最偉大的時刻，比如火的發現、獅身人面像的斷鼻子或亞瑟的傳說。揭開瘋狂兔子如何造成嚴重破壞並改變歷史進程......</desc>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<md5>cc34cf2cf16474224229f11cd2d8700f</md5>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Rabbids - Travel in Time 3D (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rabbids - Travel in Time 3D (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Rabbids - Travel in Time 3D (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="176368">
		<path>./Rhythm Paradise Megamix (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>請按一下這裡</name>
		<sortname>69 =-  Rhythm Paradise Megamix (Europe)</sortname>
		<desc>有節奏的遊戲樂趣，山羊吃蘿蔔，還有你按下按鈕聽過的最時髦的曲調？這裡一定是節奏天堂吧？超級混音。這個新鮮的組合擁有 70 多款節奏遊戲，包括新遊戲、粉絲最愛的混音遊戲以及美國首發遊戲。嘗試到達天堂世界，刺殺病毒、餵熊等等！只是不要錯過任何一個節拍。
當你深入研究每一個搞笑的隨機活動時，你會被傳奇人物創造的引人入勝的配樂帶入節奏天堂的世界......</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20150611T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<region>eu</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Rhythm Paradise Megamix (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rhythm Paradise Megamix (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Rhythm Paradise Megamix (Europe)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11204">
		<path>./Rhythm Thief &amp; the Emperor's Treasure (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Rhythm Thief &amp; the Emperor's Treasure (USA)</name>
		<sortname>70 =-  Rhythm Thief &amp; the Emperor's Treasure (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>Raphael, a normal boy by day, acts as the legendary art thief Phantom R by night. He is well-known for stealing precious paintings and returning them days later, never getting caught. His true motive can be traced back three years prior to the start of the game, where Raphael's father mysteriously disappeared and left him with a strange coin. Raphael found all of the paintings his father had stolen shortly afterward, replacing them with forgeries. As Phantom R, Raphael works to replace his father's forgeries with the original artworks, meanwhile hoping he will someday find his father again. 
At the start of the game, Raphael finds a lead in the form of a museum exhibit which is currently displaying a bracelet with the same symbol as that on his father's coin. As Phantom R publicly announces his intention to steal the bracelet, Raphael must deal with the unraveling of a mystery involving a hostile man who claims to be the historical Napoleon, a mysterious girl named Marie who seems to have some connection to him, and the whereabouts of his very own father that may put him in over his head.
Rhythm Thief &amp; the Emperor's Treasure is a mix of adventure and rhythm, following the story of a Parisian mystery. The player can explore various landmarks of Paris during their search for clues in a point-and-click style reminiscent of Professor Layton. Advancing through the plot may involve solving puzzles or, more frequently, completing a mini-game where Raphael must move to the beat. These games may make use of either the stylus or the gyroscope feature of the 3DS; depending on how closely the player has followed the rhythm, a letter rank will be given. Coins can be found throughout the city and used to buy items for use in a mini-game. Optional mini-games may also be found throughout the city, holding references to other SEGA franchises.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20120119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Music And Dance</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Rhythm Thief &amp; the Emperor's Treasure (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rhythm Thief &amp; the Emperor's Treasure (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Rhythm Thief &amp; the Emperor's Treasure (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11068">
		<path>./Rune Factory 4 (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Rune Factory 4 (USA)</name>
		<sortname>71 =-  Rune Factory 4 (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>Rune Factory 4 marks the return of the popular Harvest Moon spinoff that combines farming with dungeon adventuring. For the first time in the series, the player can select to play as a male or female hero, and potential suitors of either gender are also available in order to pursue love, marriage, and possibly a child. As the newly-appointed prince or princess, you can fulfill your royal duties of protecting the town from invaders, or take a more rural approach to governing by raising your own fruits and vegetables and helping townsfolk. Should some dungeon adventuring be on the days itinerary, you can select from the castles vast armament of swords, spears, and staffs along with magic for battle against dangerous foes, or even bring along a companion or friendly monster to aid you during your travels.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20131002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xseed Games</developer>
		<publisher>Neverland</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Rune Factory 4 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rune Factory 4 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Rune Factory 4 (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11102">
		<path>./Senran Kagura Burst (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Senran Kagura Burst (Europe)</name>
		<sortname>72 =-  Senran Kagura Burst (Europe)</sortname>
		<desc>Senran Kagura Burst is an enhanced and updated version of the original Senran Kagura. It includes the complete original game, along with an entirely new scenario starring the rival Hebijo ninja team, which tells the original story from a different perspective. A number of new outfits and unlockable missions have also been added.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20131114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tamsoft Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Xseed Games</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>eu</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Senran Kagura Burst (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Senran Kagura Burst (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Senran Kagura Burst (Europe)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11253">
		<path>./Shantae and the Pirates Curse (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Shantae and the Pirates Curse (USA)</name>
		<sortname>73 =-  Shantae and the Pirates Curse (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>Embark on a brand new adventure with Shantae, the hair-whipping belly dancing genie! When Shantae loses her genie magic, she must team up with her nemesis, the nefarious pirate Risky Boots in order to save Sequin Land from evil. As a pirate, Shantae gains new weapons and tools to advance her quest, slay monsters, battle epic bosses ?and hopefully get her magic back in the bargain! But can she really trust her most deadly enemy?</desc>
		<releasedate>20141023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wayforward</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Shantae and the Pirates Curse (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shantae and the Pirates Curse (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Shantae and the Pirates Curse (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11119">
		<path>./Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Summoner - Soul Hackers (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Summoner - Soul Hackers (USA)</name>
		<sortname>74 =-  Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Summoner - Soul Hackers (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>Soul Hackers delivers a first-person, dungeon-crawling RPG experience set in a future where technology and otherworldly forces meet in a macabre fusion of cyberpunk futurism and gothic horror. A first-person sci-fi RPG epic, Soul Hackers tells of a city held up as a beacon of humanity's triumph of technology, but with an infernal secret. In this would-be utopia, a group of hackers takes on a centuries-old mystic society, and a battle for control over humanity's fate is about to begin.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20130416T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NIS America</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Summoner - Soul Hackers (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Summoner - Soul Hackers (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Summoner - Soul Hackers (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11107">
		<path>./Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Survivor Overclocked (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Survivor Overclocked (USA)</name>
		<sortname>75 =-  Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Survivor Overclocked (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>Expanded and enhanced, Devil Survivor Overclocked for Nintendo 3DS builds upon the game's original release with the addition of voice acting for the entirety of the game's lengthy, unconventional narrative. Moreover, that very story, already boasting multiple endings based on critical decisions by the player, now concludes with a special eighth chapter, a rousing epilogue for Shin Megami Tensei fans. The game's beautifully remastered hand drawn artwork and character portraits benefit from the new system's higher resolution screens, offering players a crisper, higher fidelity experience.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Ghostlight</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Survivor Overclocked (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Survivor Overclocked (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Survivor Overclocked (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11019">
		<path>./Shin Megami Tensei IV (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Shin Megami Tensei IV (USA)</name>
		<sortname>76 =-  Shin Megami Tensei IV (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>Building on the styles of ATLUS' Persona, Devil Summoner, and Devil Survivor titles, SMTIV is the first true successor to 2004's Shin Megami Tensei: Nocturne. The story of SMTIV revolves around the Samurai, the sacred protectors of the Eastern Kingdom of Mikado. As a newly appointed Samurai, players will struggle with factions that have nefarious designs on the world as they defend their home kingdom from a growing army of demons. Decisions players make throughout the course of the story will have lasting repercussions, as the fate of the world hangs in the balance.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20130716T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Shin Megami Tensei IV (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shin Megami Tensei IV (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Shin Megami Tensei IV (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11181">
		<path>./Shinobi (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Shinobi (Europe)</name>
		<sortname>77 =-  Shinobi (Europe)</sortname>
		<desc>Betrayed by your friend you must battle an ancient and evil clan in this epic reboot of the acclaimed Shinobi series. Shinobi captures the classic side-scrolling action from the original Shinobi games. This coupled with intense combat in exotic locations and over the top boss encounters is what players have loved since the early days of the series.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20111115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Griptonite Games</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<region>eu</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Shinobi (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shinobi (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Shinobi (Europe)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11003">
		<path>./Shovel Knight (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Shovel Knight (USA)</name>
		<sortname>78 =-  Shovel Knight (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>Shovel Knight is a 2014 action platformer video game developed and published by independent developer Yacht Club Games for the Nintendo 3DS, Wii U, and personal computer platforms. The game was released worldwide on June 26, 2014. Shovel Knight was directed by former WayForward Technologies member Sean Velasco, and includes music composed by Jake Kaufman and Manami Matsumae.
Prior to the game, adventurers Shovel Knight and Shield Knight fought alongside one another, journeying across the world and seeking treasure. However, when the two explore the Tower of Fate, the two fall to the dark magic power of a cursed amulet. When Shovel Knight reawakens, the Tower has been sealed and Shield Knight is nowhere to be seen. Grieving for his beloved, Shovel Knight gives up adventuring and secludes himself. However, during his absence, the Enchantress rises to power, spreading evil across the land. Upon hearing that the Enchantress has unsealed the Tower of Fate, Shovel Knight takes up his shovel again and ventures towards it, hoping to find and rescue Shield Knight. In order to do so, Shovel Knight must fight the eight members of "The Order of No Quarter," who have been dispatched by the Enchantress to impede him.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20140626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yacht Club Games</developer>
		<publisher>Yacht Club Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Shovel Knight (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shovel Knight (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Shovel Knight (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11110">
		<path>./Sonic - Lost World (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Sonic - Lost World (Europe)</name>
		<sortname>79 =-  Sonic - Lost World (Europe)</sortname>
		<desc>Dr. Eggman has harnessed the power of six menacing creatures known as the Deadly Six, but when the Deadly Six rise up against their master, Sonic has to unite with his arch nemesis in order to take on the new enemies head-to-head. Using his dynamic new parkour moves and improved Colour Powers, Sonic must run, jump and race through a variety of ever changing terrains in order to defeat the Deadly Six.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<region>eu</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Sonic - Lost World (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sonic - Lost World (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Sonic - Lost World (Europe)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11089">
		<path>./Sonic Generations (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Sonic Generations (Europe)</name>
		<sortname>80 =-  Sonic Generations (Europe)</sortname>
		<desc>Set across three defining eras from 20 years of Sonic the Hedgehog video game history, the instantly recognisable environments of Sonic Generations have been re-built in stunning HD and are now playable in both classic side scrolling 2D from 1991, as well as modern 3D style found in Sonic's most recent adventures. Each incarnation of Sonic in Sonic Generations comes complete with his trademark special move, Spin Dash and Spin Attack for Classic Sonic, and Homing Attack and Sonic Boost for Modern Sonic. An innovative new interactive menu system allows for complete immersion in Sonic's universe with favourite characters and hidden treasures gradually being revealed throughout the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20111102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dimps</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<family>Sonic the Hedgehog</family>
		<region>eu</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Sonic Generations (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sonic Generations (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Sonic Generations (Europe)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11117">
		<path>./Star Fox 64 3D (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Star Fox 64 3D (Europe)</name>
		<sortname>81 =-  Star Fox 64 3D (Europe)</sortname>
		<desc>The Star Fox team triumphantly returns to one of its greatest missions with this remake of Star Fox 64 in full 3D, featuring a complete graphical update.
The entire Star Fox universe spreads out realistically into the depths of the Nintendo 3DS screen while the 3D visuals give the player a clearer grasp of distance and position. This makes the game more approachable and intuitive, thereby allowing players to focus on the action.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20110911T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<region>eu</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Star Fox 64 3D (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Star Fox 64 3D (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Star Fox 64 3D (Europe)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="191994">
		<path>./Story of Seasons - Trio of Towns (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Story of Seasons - Trio of Towns (USA)</name>
		<sortname>82 =-  Story of Seasons - Trio of Towns (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>What will you do today? Take charge of an expansive farm near three unique and exciting towns and choose what kind of life to lead.
The original and best-selling farming/life sim returns for its 20th anniversary with a brand new adventure!
Take on the role of a young city slicker who has always wished for a life on the farm. Your dream leads you to a huge plot of open land just ready to be filled with crops, livestock, decorations, and more.
Your new farm is at the crossroads of three different towns. Westown, with its cows and corrals, has everything the classic frontier settler needs. Right next door is Lulukoko Town, a warm, friendly paradise to rival any tropical island. Rounding out the neighborhood is Tsuyukusa, a traditional Far Eastern village. Become friends with the residents and help them improve their towns, then connect to other farmers like you, locally or via internet, to chat and trade useful items.
Grow crops, raise adorable pets, become a renowned chef or fashionista, and even discover romance with the locals. It's all up to you in STORY OF SEASONS: Trio of Towns.</desc>
		<developer>Marvelous Interactive</developer>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Story of Seasons - Trio of Towns (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Story of Seasons - Trio of Towns (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Story of Seasons - Trio of Towns (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="12017">
		<path>./Story of Seasons (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Story of Seasons (USA)</name>
		<sortname>83 =-  Story of Seasons (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>Story of Seasons is a farming simulation video game developed by Marvelous Entertainment for the Nintendo 3DS. It was released in Japan on February 27, 2014, and in North America on March 31, 2015. The game is not under the Harvest Moon title in North America due to Natsume's ownership of the name. However, less than a month later, Natsume themselves announced their own original title, not produced by Marvelous, Harvest Moon: The Lost Valley released only in North America and Europe, also released in 2014 for the Nintendo 3DS.
The game follows along the same lines as the rest of the series, in which the player takes on the role of a farmer. The player can choose to play a boy or girl farmer. The player can choose between two difficulties at the beginning of the game, but this cannot be changed once the choice is made. There are a variety of things to do in this game, such as producing crops and raising livestock. Story of Seasons introduces new characters, including a tiny goddess and a tiny witch.</desc>
		<releasedate>20150310T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xseed Games</developer>
		<publisher>Marvelous AQL</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Story of Seasons (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Story of Seasons (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Story of Seasons (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11030">
		<path>./Super Mario 3D Land (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Super Mario 3D Land (USA)</name>
		<sortname>84 =-  Super Mario 3D Land (USA)</sortname>
		<desc>Super Mario 3D Land is a platform game that has been described by game designer Shigeru Miyamoto as a "3D Mario that plays as a 2D Mario game." As such, Super Mario 3D Land combines the elements of traditional side-scrolling Mario titles, such as linear-based levels, with those of the modern open world Mario titles, such as moving Mario in three dimensions and performing a variety of actions. Similar to the classic side-scrolling Mario games, the objective of each level is to reach and grab the "Goal Pole" located at the end of the course before the time limit expires. Super Mario 3D Land utilizes a similar health system to those games, in which Mario shrinks upon taking damage from enemies or hazards, and damage while as "Small Mario" results in losing a life.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20111113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Super Mario 3D Land (USA)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Mario 3D Land (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Super Mario 3D Land (USA)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="190672">
		<path>./Taiko no Tatsujin - Don to Katsu no Jikuu Daibouken (Japan) (Translated En).3ds</path>
		<name>Taiko no Tatsujin - Don to Katsu no Jikuu Daibouken (Japan) (Translated En)</name>
		<sortname>85 =-  Taiko no Tatsujin - Don to Katsu no Jikuu Daibouken (Japan) (Translated En)</sortname>
		<releasedate>20140626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Music And Dance</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<region>jp</region>
		<lang>en,jp</lang>
		<image>./images/Taiko no Tatsujin - Don to Katsu no Jikuu Daibouken (Japan) (Translated En)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Taiko no Tatsujin - Don to Katsu no Jikuu Daibouken (Japan) (Translated En)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Taiko no Tatsujin - Don to Katsu no Jikuu Daibouken (Japan) (Translated En)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11159">
		<path>./Tekken 3D - Prime Edition (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Tekken 3D - Prime Edition (Europe)</name>
		<sortname>86 =-  Tekken 3D - Prime Edition (Europe)</sortname>
		<desc>Play the game, watch the movie!
Tekken 3D Prime Edition contains the complete entertainment world of TEKKEN onto a single Nintendo 3DS card!
Play the game, watch the movie! Tekken 3D Prime Edition contains the complete entertainment world of TEKKEN onto a single Nintendo 3DS card! Battle with more than 40 fighters from the TEKKEN universe and with Young Heihachi for the first time ever! In addition, watch TEKKEN: Blood Vengeance, a full 3D theatrical experience produced by Digital Frontier in conjunction with the Tekken Project development team. With the satisfying combination of a movie and fully featured portable Tekken gaming experience, players can take TEKKEN wherever they go.
Tekken Experience ? Contains the complete TEKKEN: Blood Vengeance 3D movie and the intense fighting action of the TEKKEN series in one package
Card Collector ? Amass your collection of original Tekken Cards in-game or obtain using StreetPass to find them all
Time to Fight ? Play in multiple single player modes or take the battle to the streets through Local Play and Internet Play
Bloody Vengeance ? Watch the full length theatrical feature TEKKEN: Blood Vengeance in full 3D through the Nintendo 3DS system</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20120216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>2</players>
		<family>Tekken</family>
		<region>eu</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Tekken 3D - Prime Edition (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tekken 3D - Prime Edition (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Tekken 3D - Prime Edition (Europe)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="12079">
		<path>./Terraria (USA) (Rev 1) Decrypted.3ds</path>
		<name>Terraria (USA) (Rev 1) Decrypted</name>
		<sortname>87 =-  Terraria (USA) (Rev 1) Decrypted</sortname>
		<desc>Terraria is a two dimensional platform game of exploration and crafting. Players can use mines and picks to collect various items from the environment including wood, ore and even spider webs. Resources acquired from the environment can be placed or crafted into all manner of items.
The simple crafting system automatically lists any item that you have the materials to craft. First priority is to set up a base before night fall hits in order to protect yourself from roving zombies and eyeball monsters. You can craft many items for your home, including doors, walls, tables, chairs and beds.
During the daytime slimes roam the land and must be avoided or dispatched with a weapon such as a sword or axe. As you gather materials you will be able to construct more powerful weapons from different ores as well as armor to protect yourself.
30 monsters are present in the game including slimes, floating eyeballs, giant earth worms and zombies.
Building a nice home will attract NPC (non-player characters) to your house to set up residence. These can include a merchant to trade with and nurses who can heal your wounds.
Terraria supports single player,  multi-player servers and player vs player combat.</desc>
		<developer>Re-Logic</developer>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<md5>62726d37938010ee9cb4757f2425766e</md5>
		<region>us</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Terraria (USA) (Rev 1) Decrypted-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Terraria (USA) (Rev 1) Decrypted-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Terraria (USA) (Rev 1) Decrypted-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11007">
		<path>./Tomodachi Life (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Tomodachi Life (Europe)</name>
		<sortname>88 =-  Tomodachi Life (Europe)</sortname>
		<desc>Tomodachi Life is a communication game for the 3DS in which players can convert their Miis into Tomodachis (or create new ones) and put them in a wide range of scenarios ranging from charming to utterly ridiculous. A key feature of the game is its text-to-speech tech which outputs user generated text as computerized speech in seven languages (EFIGS, Japanese and Korean).</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20130418T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>eu</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Tomodachi Life (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tomodachi Life (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Tomodachi Life (Europe)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11059">
		<path>./Yu-Gi-Oh! Zexal - World Duel Carnival.3ds</path>
		<name>Yu-Gi-Oh! Zexal - World Duel Carnival</name>
		<sortname>89 =-  Yu-Gi-Oh! Zexal - World Duel Carnival</sortname>
		<desc>Play as yourself or one of eleven playable characters from the series, like Yuma, Astral, Tori, Shark and more, each with their own storyline and earn an invite to the World Duel Carnival where you can battle with more than 40 Duelists from the TV show! Players can enjoy a Story Mode and a Free Duel Mode where they can play with more than 5,700 cards.
-The very first Yu-Gi-Oh! ZEXAL video game and the first Yu-Gi-Oh! video game available for the Nintendo 3DS handheld system.
-Twelve playable characters, each with a unique storyline that can be experienced through Story Mode.
-Battle with more than 40 colorful Duelists.
-Customize your Deck with more than 5,700 cards from the official Yu-Gi-Oh! TRADING CARD GAME.
-In-game animated cinematics, and exciting Monster summon effects bring Duels to life.
-Explore all the options in Free Duel Mode and customize card sleeves, game mats, and even Deck Lists to Duel for hours.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Playing Cards</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Yu-Gi-Oh! Zexal - World Duel Carnival-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Yu-Gi-Oh! Zexal - World Duel Carnival-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Yu-Gi-Oh! Zexal - World Duel Carnival-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="11086">
		<path>./Zero Escape - Virtue's Last Reward (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Zero Escape - Virtue's Last Reward (Europe)</name>
		<sortname>90 =-  Zero Escape - Virtue's Last Reward (Europe)</sortname>
		<desc>You thought you'd defeated the Nonary Game, but now it's back, and more deadly than ever. It'll take cunning, skill, and more than a little luck to escape alive, but do you really have a choice?
IDO agents working in California report that preliminary findings indicate the exceedingly dangerous Japanese adventure game known as "Zennin Shiboudesu" has somehow crossed the Pacific. Attempts were made to contain it, but some carriers seem to have escaped the quarantine and are now at large.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20121023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rising Star Games</developer>
		<publisher>Chunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<players>1</players>
		<region>eu</region>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<image>./images/Zero Escape - Virtue's Last Reward (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Zero Escape - Virtue's Last Reward (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Zero Escape - Virtue's Last Reward (Europe)-image.png</mix>
	</game>
	<game id="176095">
		<path>./Ever Oasis (Europe).cxi</path>
		<name>Ever Oasis</name>
		<desc>The desert's last safe haven is a lone oasis you call home. So draw a line in the sand and fight to protect it! As you explore the desert and solve puzzling dungeons, you'll gather resources to build up your oasis with the water spirit Esna. Allies will join your cause, so equip them with weapons, and use their skills to slay towering bosses.

The Ever Oasisâ„¢ game is a new action-adventure RPG grown from the ground up by Koichi Ishii, creator of the Mana series and producer at GREZZO, the studio that rebuilt multiple The Legend of Zeldaâ„¢ games for the Nintendo 3DSâ„¢ family of systems. Their team has crafted puzzles and traps too perilous for one hero to solve. So recruit a party of allies and level up their stats to learn new battle skills. Then return to your oasis and restore it: choose which shops to build, stock their inventories, collect a share of the profits, and keep villagers happy by fulfilling requests. Before long your oasis will blossom into a beacon of hope for all walks of life in the desert. Don't let them down.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ever Oasis (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Ever Oasis (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ever Oasis (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Ever Oasis (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<releasedate>20170623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Grezzo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games / Action RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>27 =-  Ever Oasis (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103608" />
	</game>
	<game id="11626">
		<path>./50 Classic Games 3D (USA).cxi</path>
		<name>50 Classic Games 3D</name>
		<desc>Nintendo.com Description (from Ad Blurbs)It?s all right here, in 50 Classic Games for Nintendo 3DS! With new 
eye-popping graphics and interactive features, you?ll get lost for hours 
in the wildly entertaining games that range from backgammon to 
brainteasers! Try your hand at Texas Hold?Em, Blackjack, and Roulette. 
Rediscover classic board and dice games like Farkle, Chess, and 
Mahjongg. Go fishing, play air hockey, take out enemy battleships, and 
throw darts! Solve tricky brainteasers, picture puzzles, and more!


Features


? Try your hand at Texas Hold?Em and Roulette? Play 
games like Farkle, Chess, and Mahjongg? Go fishing, play air hockey, 
and throw darts!? Solve tricky brainteasers, picture puzzles, and 
more!</desc>
		<image>./images/50 Classic Games 3D (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/50 Classic Games 3D (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/50 Classic Games 3D (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/50 Classic Games 3D (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20120424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cerasus Media</developer>
		<publisher>Maximum Family Games, LLC</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>b82e62f18127b1a9382c08d0839187c0</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>02 =-  50 Classic Games 3D (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103559" />
	</game>
	<game id="176106">
		<path>./Fire Emblem Fates - Conquest (USA) Decrypted.3ds</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem Fates: Conquest</name>
		<desc>Two kingdoms are on the brink of war. Whose side will you choose? Torn between two families, you're an heir of Hoshido, raised by Nohrian royals. If you walk the path of Conquest, you must fight to change your misguided kingdom from within. Command warriors with expert precision and forge deep relationships to master this turn-based strategy game.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fire Emblem Fates - Conquest (USA) Decrypted-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Fire Emblem Fates - Conquest (USA) Decrypted-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fire Emblem Fates - Conquest (USA) Decrypted-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Fire Emblem Fates - Conquest (USA) Decrypted-image.png</mix>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>34 =-  Fire Emblem Fates - Conquest (USA) Decrypted</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103607" />
	</game>
	<game id="11758">
		<path>./Face Racers - Photo Finish (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Face Racers - Photo Finish</name>
		<desc>Start your turbo-charged engines and blast into the outrageous arcade racing game, Face Racers: Photo Finish, with photo customizable 3D racers that put YOU in the game! Available on the Nintendo 3DS, Face Racers delivers unique, in-your-face gameplay, with dangerous obstacles that come to life in 3D right before your eyes! Take photos with your 3DS camera and place them on the face of your custom 3D racer, billboards and power-ups. Take on friends in multiplayer mode for a true photo finish in Face Racers!

Features

? Use your photo to customize your racer, billboards, and power-ups!? Challenge up to 3 friends in local and online multiplayer.? Take control of the wheel with 3DS tilt-steering.</desc>
		<image>./images/Face Racers - Photo Finish (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Face Racers - Photo Finish (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Face Racers - Photo Finish (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Face Racers - Photo Finish (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<releasedate>20110906T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Renegade Kid</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<md5>a5f262f6398ef8fcfc349d203c0c04f4</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>29 =-  Face Racers - Photo Finish (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103607" />
	</game>
	<game id="11365">
		<path>./Crush3d.3ds</path>
		<name>CRUSH3D</name>
		<desc>Danny is troubled with insomnia. Desperate for sleep and unable to get it, he finds himself a test subject in the mad Dr. Reubens' crowning achievement, C.R.U.S.H. (or Cognitive Regression Utilizing pSychiatric Heuristics, if you prefer). C.R.U.S.H. puts the subject under hypnosis and allows them to explore their psyche and confront their own deep, dark secrets.</desc>
		<image>./images/Crush3d-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Crush3d-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Crush3d-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Crush3d-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20120215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zoë Mode</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<sortname>16 =-  Crush3d</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103606" />
	</game>
	<game id="176236">
		<path>./Mario &amp; Luigi - Superstar Saga + Bowser's Minions (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Luigi: Superstar Saga + Bowser's Minions</name>
		<desc>Save Princess Peach's voice, the Beanbean Kingdom and ... Bowser?!



The game that launched the Mario &amp; Luigi series returns looking better than ever before. In this renewed classic, Mario and Luigi journey to the Beanbean Kingdom with Bowser to restore Princess Peach?s voice. Control Mario and Luigi simultaneously, making use of their unique Bros. Moves to solve puzzles and emerge victorious in action-packed battles. Pay heed to the enemy?s patterns and time your reactions right to land satisfying counterblows. Included in this remake is the Minion Quest: The Search for Bowser mode, which tells the story of the game from the perspective of Bowser?s minions. Recruit characters to grow your own Minion army as you fight to locate your missing leader!

Features:

Mario and Luigi have access to different techniques, known as Bros. Moves, necessary for solving puzzles on their adventure. Switch between the two characters at will to pave your way and progress through new areas.
Time your button presses to skillfully dodge enemy blows, land devastating counters, and inflict increased damage in battle. Utilize Bros. Attacks that dish out massive damage!
In the brand new mode titled Minion Quest: The Search for Bowser, become the unlikely hero, Captain Goomba. Journey together with ShyGuy, Boo and other familiar Baddies.
The Minion Quest storyline takes place during Mario &amp; Luigi?s classic adventure. Find out what really transpired behind-the-scenes!
Compatible with amiibo? figures* from the Super Mario series, including Mario and Luigi amiibo figures. Also coming soon are brand new Goomba and Koopa Troopa amiibo. The Goomba, Koopa Troopa and Boo amiibo figures will each have read/write compatibility.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mario &amp; Luigi - Superstar Saga + Bowser's Minions (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Mario &amp; Luigi - Superstar Saga + Bowser's Minions (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mario &amp; Luigi - Superstar Saga + Bowser's Minions (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Mario &amp; Luigi - Superstar Saga + Bowser's Minions (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20171006T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alphadream Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Mario</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>48 =-  Mario &amp; Luigi - Superstar Saga + Bowser's Minions (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103607" />
	</game>
	<game id="11135">
		<path>./F1 2011 (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>F1 2011</name>
		<desc>F1 2011 is the handheld adaptation of the main F1 2011 game. It offers the full 2011 racing season with all stages and it incorporates the multi-season career mode from the main game. In addition there are Grand Prix weekends and three-lap sprints. Grand Prix events are split up in practice runs, qualifying sessions and the main races themselves. There are driving aids (including determining the race distance), weather effects, fuel and tires options, and it includes the KERS and DRS systems from the main version.

Unique to the handheld versions is a number of mini-game challenges such as checkpoints races, overtaking, autocross-style slaloms or racing in specific situations such as the last two laps of a race in the rain with the wrong tires equipped. They are organized in tiers with a bonus one at the end. The performance in these challenges is ranked with a letter. The game can be played online and for the 3DS StreetPass is used to unlock rival ghosts. Both versions support multiplayer, local as well as online, in head-to-head time trails or in a full Grand Prix. On the Vita the front touch screen is used to change the camera and the rear touch pad can be used as an optional substitute for actions such as braking and throttling.

Differences from the console version include downgraded graphics, a simplified damage model and certain animated sequences that have been cut.</desc>
		<image>./images/F1 2011 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/F1 2011 (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/F1 2011 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/F1 2011 (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>Sumo Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>28 =-  F1 2011 (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103618" />
	</game>
	<game id="10998">
		<path>./Bravely Default (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Bravely Default</name>
		<desc>This new yet traditional offering from Square Enix captures the charm and elegant and simplicity of yesteryear's canonical RPGs. Become a Warrior of Light and journey to the land of Luxemdarc in this classic tale of personal growth and adventure.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bravely Default (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Bravely Default (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bravely Default (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Bravely Default (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20121011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Silicon Studio</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>09 =-  Bravely Default (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103613" />
	</game>
	<game id="11094">
		<path>./Dead or Alive - Dimensions (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Dead Or Alive - Dimensions</name>
		<desc>DEAD OR ALIVE Dimensions takes the vivacious characters and locales that have made the DOA franchise a hit with gamers everywhere and presents them in eye-popping 3D. All of the punches, kicks, counters and holds that have defined the series as a top-tier fighter are present for the first time on a portable gaming system - the Nintendo 3DS. DEAD OR ALIVE Dimensions features some of the best content from the series spanning all of the titles from the original DOA up to DOA 4.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dead or Alive - Dimensions (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Dead or Alive - Dimensions (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dead or Alive - Dimensions (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Dead or Alive - Dimensions (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20110524T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Ninja</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>18 =-  Dead or Alive - Dimensions (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103623" />
	</game>
	<game id="11032">
		<path>./Etrian Odyssey Untold The Millennium Girl (USA).cxi</path>
		<name>Etrian Odyssey Untold: The Millennium Girl</name>
		<desc>Etrian Odyssey Untold is a game in two parts: the first part is a story-driven first person adventure into the world of Etria. Appropriate for players new to the series and veterans alike, the Story mode gives players five pre-made characters, each with their own personalities and dialogue to explore a side of Etria not seen in the first game. Adventurers must brave new dungeon layouts, floors, and enemies to find out the truth of the Yggdrasil Tree and the mysterious girl, Frederica.

For series veterans, Classic mode offers the traditional Etrian Odyssey gameplay, updated to the latest conveniences found in Etrian Odyssey IV, including full 3-D graphics. The game also includes animated opening and story cutscenes by MADHOUSE Inc. and voiceovers for the story and battle scenes, plus the option for orchestrated background music.</desc>
		<image>./images/Etrian Odyssey Untold The Millennium Girl (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Etrian Odyssey Untold The Millennium Girl (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Etrian Odyssey Untold The Millennium Girl (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Etrian Odyssey Untold The Millennium Girl (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20131001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>26 =-  Etrian Odyssey Untold The Millennium Girl (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103623" />
	</game>
	<game id="11009">
		<path>./Mario Kart 7 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Pt,Ru) (Rev 1) Decrypted.3ds</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 7</name>
		<desc>The newest installment of the fan-favorite Mario Kart franchise brings Mushroom Kingdom racing fun into glorious 3D. For the first time, drivers explore new competitive kart possibilities, such as soaring through the skies or plunging to the depths of the sea. New courses, strategic new abilities and customizable karts bring the racing excitement to new heights.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mario Kart 7 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Pt,Ru) (Rev 1) Decrypted-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Mario Kart 7 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Pt,Ru) (Rev 1) Decrypted-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mario Kart 7 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Pt,Ru) (Rev 1) Decrypted-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Mario Kart 7 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Pt,Ru) (Rev 1) Decrypted-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20111201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Retro Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Mario Kart</family>
		<players>2-8</players>
		<lang>ru,pt,nl,it,es,de,fr,en</lang>
		<region>ru</region>
		<sortname>51 =-  Mario Kart 7 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Pt,Ru) (Rev 1) Decrypted</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103623" />
	</game>
	<game id="11062">
		<path>./Etrian Odyssey IV - Legends of the Titan (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Etrian Odyssey 4 - Legends Of The Titan</name>
		<desc>For centuries, the tree Yggdrasil has been a constant presence in the lives of the people of Tharsis. It looms on the horizon, visible from everywhere in the city. But its roots are in a far-off land where no one has ventured until the Outland Count of Tharsis sponsors an Explorers Guild to reach Yggdrasil and discover its secrets. You are the latest explorer arriving in Tharsis to seek your fame and fortune. Board your skyship and set out into the clouds in search of treasure, glory, and the answer to Tharsis' oldest mystery.</desc>
		<image>./images/Etrian Odyssey IV - Legends of the Titan (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Etrian Odyssey IV - Legends of the Titan (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Etrian Odyssey IV - Legends of the Titan (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Etrian Odyssey IV - Legends of the Titan (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20130226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NIS America</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>25 =-  Etrian Odyssey IV - Legends of the Titan (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103628" />
	</game>
	<game id="11051">
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country Returns 3D (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country Returns 3D</name>
		<desc>Over 70 levels of banana-hoarding fun featuring Donkey Kong and Diddy Kong. Run, jump, climb and defeat enemies through diverse environments until you retrieve Donkey Kong's stolen banana hoard. Rebuilt and optimized for portable play on the Nintendo 3DS system.</desc>
		<image>./images/Donkey Kong Country Returns 3D (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Donkey Kong Country Returns 3D (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Donkey Kong Country Returns 3D (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Donkey Kong Country Returns 3D (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20130524T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Retro Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>19 =-  Donkey Kong Country Returns 3D (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103628" />
	</game>
	<game id="11056">
		<path>./Legend of Korra - A New Era Begins, The (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>The Legend of Korra: A New Era Begins</name>
		<desc>Join Korra and her friends to stop an ancient evil that has emerged from the portal and threatens the balance of both worlds!



Original Avatar storyline penned by the TV show's creators.

Wield the power of all 4 elements?water, earth, fire, and air as only the Avatar can!

Take control of Korra and her friends in strategic battles spanning the world.

Beat overwhelming odds by activating the all-powerful Avatar state.</desc>
		<image>./images/Legend of Korra - A New Era Begins, The (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Legend of Korra - A New Era Begins, The (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Legend of Korra - A New Era Begins, The (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Legend of Korra - A New Era Begins, The (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Webfoot</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>41 =-  Legend of Korra - A New Era Begins, The (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103640" />
	</game>
	<game id="11312">
		<path>./Cooking Mama 5 - Bon Appetit! (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Cooking Mama 5 : Bon Appétit !</name>
		<desc>Cooking Mama 5: Bon AppÃ©tit! (ã‚¯ãƒƒã‚­ãƒ³ã‚°ãƒžãƒžï¼• Kukkingu Mama 5) is the sequel to the Nintendo 3DS video game Cooking Mama 4: Kitchen Magic and is the fifth installment to the Cooking Mama series on the Nintendo 3DS. It was released in Japan on November 21, 2013, on September 16, 2014 in North America [2] and on March 6, 2015 in Europe.[3] It contains over 60 recipes and new household activities/games.[4]</desc>
		<image>./images/Cooking Mama 5 - Bon Appetit! (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Cooking Mama 5 - Bon Appetit! (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cooking Mama 5 - Bon Appetit! (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Cooking Mama 5 - Bon Appetit! (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20140916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cooking Mama</developer>
		<publisher>505 Games</publisher>
		<genre>Various</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>14 =-  Cooking Mama 5 - Bon Appetit! (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103642" />
	</game>
	<game id="12009">
		<path>./Flap Flap (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Flap Flap</name>
		<desc>Summon up all your skill, precision and nerves of steel: Flap Flap won'tgo easy on you!


Bit of a lightweight? Then all the bonuses and special abilities will come in handy?


Unfortunately, there are also enemies and obstacles to make things complicated, too!</desc>
		<image>./images/Flap Flap (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Flap Flap (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Flap Flap (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Flap Flap (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<developer>Bigben Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Sanuk Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<md5>a962fd6d05e14331650ded27c50fc8cf</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>35 =-  Flap Flap (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103644" />
	</game>
	<game id="11106">
		<path>./Code Name - S.T.E.A.M. (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Code Name S.t.e.a.m</name>
		<desc>Launch S.T.E.A.M., an elite team of steam-powered special-forces soldiers, to save the world from an alien menace. In this new blend of action and strategy, our commandos use steam power stored in special backpacks to move into position and fire an arsenal of distinct weapons. Pick your team members and load out, then use strategy to decide the best way to approach this steampunk-inspired battlefield.</desc>
		<image>./images/Code Name - S.T.E.A.M. (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Code Name - S.T.E.A.M. (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Code Name - S.T.E.A.M. (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Code Name - S.T.E.A.M. (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Intelligent Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>12 =-  Code Name - S.T.E.A.M. (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103646" />
	</game>
	<game id="11076">
		<path>./Dragon Quest VII - Fragments of the Forgotten Past (USA).cxi</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest VII: Fragments of the Forgotten Past</name>
		<desc>Travel to the past to save the present in this classic Dragon Quest adventure that has been completely remade from the ground up for Nintendo 3DS. The world has been rebuilt, the characters have new 3D models and the story has been completely re-localized. Even customize your party with over 30 classes and rank up in turn-based battles to learn new spells and abilities.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dragon Quest VII - Fragments of the Forgotten Past (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Dragon Quest VII - Fragments of the Forgotten Past (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dragon Quest VII - Fragments of the Forgotten Past (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Dragon Quest VII - Fragments of the Forgotten Past (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20160916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Dragon Quest</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>21 =-  Dragon Quest VII - Fragments of the Forgotten Past (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103653" />
	</game>
	<game id="10989">
		<path>./Fantasy Life.3ds</path>
		<name>Fantasy Life</name>
		<desc>FANTASY LIFE* is an original RPG for the Nintendo 3DS from LEVEL-5, featuring music by Nobuo Uematsu and image illustration by Yoshitaka Amano. 
Set in a beautiful and vast open world, players create their own avatars and take up a vocation of their choosing, living out their lives as they see fit. You can set out on an adventure to save the world, or spend your days in leisurely pursuits such as cooking or fishing. Find the meaning of your new life in the limitless possibilities that reside in FANTASY LIFE* on the Nintendo 3DS</desc>
		<image>./images/Fantasy Life-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Fantasy Life-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fantasy Life-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Fantasy Life-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20140101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Brownie Brown</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220219T152127</lastplayed>
		<gametime>224</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<sortname>30 =-  Fantasy Life</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103651" />
	</game>
	<game id="11021">
		<path>./Kirby - Triple Deluxe.3ds</path>
		<name>Kirby : Triple Deluxe</name>
		<desc>Pink? Check. Puffy? Check. Powerful? You have no idea. 

Devour trees, obstacles, and huge chunks of stages with Kirbyâ€™s Hypernova ability and inhale enemies to copy epic new moves like Archer. Itâ€™s a grand new Kirbyâ„¢ adventure PLUS a new multiplayer battle mode, Kirby Fighters! 

When a mysterious being kidnaps King Dedede atop a giant Dreamstalk, only Kirby can save the day! Jump from the foreground to the background in dynamic 3D side-scrolling environments while using new and returning copy abilities to defeat enemies. Duke it out in Kirby Fighters, a fierce 4-player battle mode where you fight using a chosen ability like Sword or Ninja. The last Kirby standing reigns supreme. Whether youâ€™re new to Kirby or an old fan, the Kirby: Triple Deluxe game offers a triple threat - action, adventure, and a battle mode!</desc>
		<image>./images/Kirby - Triple Deluxe-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Kirby - Triple Deluxe-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Kirby - Triple Deluxe-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Kirby - Triple Deluxe-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20140111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Kirby</family>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<sortname>39 =-  Kirby - Triple Deluxe</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103655" />
	</game>
	<game id="176223">
		<path>./LEGO Star Wars - The Force Awakens (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>LEGO Star Wars: The Force Awakens</name>
		<desc>LEGO Star Wars: The Force Awakens marks the triumphant return of the No. 1 LEGO videogame franchise and immerses fans in the new Star Wars adventure like never before. Players can relive the epic action from the blockbuster film in a way that only LEGO can offer, featuring all of the storylines from Star Wars: The Force Awakens, retold through the clever and witty LEGO lens. The game will also feature exclusive playable content that takes players on adventures between Star Wars: Episode VI: Return of the Jedi and Star Wars: The Force Awakens, providing additional insight about the new movie and its characters.</desc>
		<image>./images/LEGO Star Wars - The Force Awakens (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/LEGO Star Wars - The Force Awakens (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/LEGO Star Wars - The Force Awakens (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/LEGO Star Wars - The Force Awakens (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>45 =-  LEGO Star Wars - The Force Awakens (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103659" />
	</game>
	<game id="10992">
		<path>./Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate</name>
		<desc>The popular fantasy action franchise Monster Hunter is now one of the most iconic gaming series in the world selling over 21 million copies worldwide since the series began in 2004. Players take on the role of a hunter and are sent to explore a settlement within the Monster Hunter universe, completing quests on their journey to seek and slay monsters whilst improving their skills and earning equipment upgrades. With many challenging monsters and over 200 quests the latest edition to the series is set to be the most expansive offering to date. Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate utilizes the functionalities of the Nintendo 3DS system to provide players with a truly intuitive hunting experience. The touch screen feature allows players to quickly access in-game books, weapons, field maps and mini games whilst the high quality graphics 3D visuals of Nintendo 3DS powered by the latest iteration of Capcom's MT Framework deliver a unique and stunning world for players to explore. Taking advantage of the portability of Nintendo 3DS, players can exchange their guild card that contains all their hunter's information with other players via StreetPass. Players can experience the world of Monster Hunter alone or in four player local play using Nintendo 3DS. Finding nearby hunters to adventure on quests with is now even easier via the local Nintendo 3DS search feature. Wii U players will be able to enjoy the hunt with Nintendo 3DS players via a local wireless connection. Gamers that own both a Wii U and Nintendo 3DS can take advantage of the inter compatibility of save data between the two consoles, taking the hunt from the living room wherever they go.</desc>
		<image>./images/Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20130302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>54 =-  Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103658" />
	</game>
	<game id="11246">
		<path>./Cooking Mama 4 (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Cooking Mama 4</name>
		<desc>Join the original digital chef as she makes her debut on Nintendo 3DS with Cooking Mama 4: Kitchen Magic! From new recipes and ways to play to fresh kitchen activities and dish combinations, the iconic kitchen cutie has some tricks up her sleeve that will magically transform kitchen newbies into master culinary artists! Slice, dice, knead, toss and flip your way through more than 200 unique Touch Screen mini-games as you cook in brand new ways with the Nintendo 3DS gyroscope: crack eggs, flip pans, balance plates and much more. Earn bronze, silver and gold medals while mixing up over 60 recipes that range from side dishes to full meals. Organize, decorate and clean your kitchen while watching surprising 3D events unfold as you prepare each meal.</desc>
		<image>./images/Cooking Mama 4 (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Cooking Mama 4 (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cooking Mama 4 (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Cooking Mama 4 (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20111011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cooking Mama</developer>
		<publisher>505 Games</publisher>
		<genre>Various</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>13 =-  Cooking Mama 4 (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103659" />
	</game>
	<game id="11241">
		<path>./Ace Combat - Assault Horizon Legacy (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Ace Combat: Assault Horizon Legacy</name>
		<desc>Ace Combat: Assault Horizon Legacy is a flight-sim / arcade fighter combat action game.  The game is typically played in a 3rd-Person, behind the aircraft, or 1st-Person, inside the cockpit view.  It features series mainstays such as numerous selectable aircraft and the ability to purchase parts and weapons to customize the fighters.  Where Assault Horizon Legacy sets itself apart from current console versions of Assault Horizon in that the gameplay is tipped more in favor of the arcade-style action of the early games in the series rather than focusing on flight-sim characteristics.  Also different from the console versions of Assault Horizon is that this entry takes place in the fictional universe of the older games in the series, rather than real-world locations.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ace Combat - Assault Horizon Legacy (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Ace Combat - Assault Horizon Legacy (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ace Combat - Assault Horizon Legacy (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Ace Combat - Assault Horizon Legacy (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20111115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Access Games</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220219T151726</lastplayed>
		<gametime>296</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>03 =-  Ace Combat - Assault Horizon Legacy (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103659" />
	</game>
	<game id="11031">
		<path>./Kingdom Hearts 3D - Dream Drop Distance (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Kingdom Hearts 3D: Dream Drop Distance</name>
		<desc>With the threat of the evil Xehanort's return, King Mickey and Yen Sid have begun preparations to combat him.  Their first step is to turn Keyblade wielders Sora and Riku into Keyblade Masters.  Sora and Riku are given the task of completing the Mark of Mastery exam which when completed will help them obtain a great power to aid in the fight against Xehanort.  This test will not be so easy as the two must venture together into seven Sleeping Worlds and find the the Keyholes of Sleep to awaken them.  Along the way they meet new friends and face new enemies in worlds completely new to them.  These challenges will forever test their abilities and lead to an ultimate test to prevent the darkness from overtaken their light.

Dream Drop Distance takes place immediately after the events of Kingdom Hearts II.  Sora learns from a letter he receives from King Mickey that he is the only one who can save those lost who are connected to him; referring to the characters Ventus, Aqua, and Terra from Birth by Sleep.  Sora and Riku travel to worlds based on settings from various Disney properties such as La Cité des Cloches (The Hunchback of Notre Dame), Prankster's Paradise (Pinnochio), Symphony of Sorcery (Fantasia) and The Grid (Tron).  

The game utilizes a gameplay mechanic called Flowmotion which allows your character to quickly bounce off walls and scale buildings in short bursts of speed.  A Drop system has been implemented which changes the control of your character to either Sora or Riku after a certain amount of time.  While playing as Sora/Riku and the Drop Gauge reaches 0, your character will switch to the other who can be in an entirely different world at a completely different time.  The game is an action-RPG with gameplay similar to Birth by Sleep in which it uses the Command Deck system.  The Command Deck lets you create your own customized deck of actions such as items and spells for quick use.  Dream Eaters are introduced as new enemies.  Some of these Dream Eaters known as Spirits can be recruited and further enhance your abilities in-game by strengthening your powers and giving you new attacks.</desc>
		<image>./images/Kingdom Hearts 3D - Dream Drop Distance (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Kingdom Hearts 3D - Dream Drop Distance (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Kingdom Hearts 3D - Dream Drop Distance (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Kingdom Hearts 3D - Dream Drop Distance (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20120731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>38 =-  Kingdom Hearts 3D - Dream Drop Distance (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103707" />
	</game>
	<game id="11385">
		<path>./Bella Sara 2 (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Bella Sara 2</name>
		<image>./images/Bella Sara 2 (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Bella Sara 2 (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bella Sara 2 (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Bella Sara 2 (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<releasedate>20110101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bigben Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Bigben Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>7feb8e8699ede9036a99b3a3bd173cd7</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>08 =-  Bella Sara 2 (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103659" />
	</game>
	<game id="11148">
		<path>./Mario &amp; Sonic at the London 2012 Olympic Games (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Sonic at the London 2012 Olympic Games</name>
		<desc>Arriving on Nintendo's new handheld system for the first time ever Mario &amp; Sonic at the London 2012 Olympic Games contains over 50 original Olympic themed events playable in both single and multiplayer modes. Bringing a whole new dimension to the Mario &amp; Sonic universe, the glasses-free 3D visuals and the unique control systems mean there are plenty of new and exciting ways to compete for a coveted gold medal!</desc>
		<image>./images/Mario &amp; Sonic at the London 2012 Olympic Games (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Mario &amp; Sonic at the London 2012 Olympic Games (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mario &amp; Sonic at the London 2012 Olympic Games (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Mario &amp; Sonic at the London 2012 Olympic Games (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20111115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<family>Mario &amp; Sonic</family>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>49 =-  Mario &amp; Sonic at the London 2012 Olympic Games (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103712" />
	</game>
	<game id="11011">
		<path>./Luigi's Mansion 2 (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Luigi's Mansion 2</name>
		<desc>After the happenings of Luigi's Mansion, Luigi once again has to put on his ghostbusting gear. This time he visits Evershade Valley, where the destruction of the Dark Moon caused all ghosts to become hostile to humans. Luigi is hired by the eccentric professor Gadd to visit five haunted mansions to retrieve the Dark Moon parts.

Luigi's weapon of choice is vacuum device called PolterGust 5000 which is used to fight against the numerous ghost enemies. The basic procedure is always the same: Luigi has to stun the ghosts with the flashlight (in contrast to the predecessor, now the position and angle is important) so he can vacuum them in. Of course the ghosts struggle against it, so their movement has to be countered with the analogue stick. There are different kinds of enemies which require a variation of tactics, e.g. some ghosts have sunglasses which have to be removed first and others are only vulnerable briefly. There are also multi-stage bossfights. 

The PolterGust 5000 is also used to solve puzzles, for example by sucking in a stove and using the flames to ignite something else. It is also a good idea to use the vacuum device on physical objects in the mansions in order to find secret passages or treasure. When Luigi picks up enough treasure, the PolterGust 5000 is automatically upgraded.

Besides the campaign, there is also a multiplayer mode which takes place in the ScareScraper, mansion with 25 floors. The available modes are hunter (sucking in as many ghosts as possible in a limited amount of time), rush (finding the exit in a limited amount of time; clocks can be picked up to extend the time limit) and polterpup (tracking down polterpulps, invisible ghosts, with the flashlight).</desc>
		<image>./images/Luigi's Mansion 2 (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Luigi's Mansion 2 (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Luigi's Mansion 2 (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Luigi's Mansion 2 (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20130101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Next Level Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>47 =-  Luigi's Mansion 2 (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103712" />
	</game>
	<game id="176265">
		<path>./Monster Hunter Generations (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Monster Hunter Generations</name>
		<desc>Monster Hunter Generations is an action role-playing video game developed and published by Capcom for the Nintendo 3DS. Announced in May 2015, the game was released in Japan in November 2015, under the title Monster Hunter Cross, and was released internationally in July 2016. Like other titles in the Monster Hunter series, players undertake quests that involve hunting dangerous creatures. Major additions in this installment include special attacks, new combat styles, and the ability to play as Felynes, who have traditionally only appeared as a companion to the player.</desc>
		<image>./images/Monster Hunter Generations (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Monster Hunter Generations (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Monster Hunter Generations (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Monster Hunter Generations (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<releasedate>20160715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>55 =-  Monster Hunter Generations (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103718" />
	</game>
	<game id="176104">
		<path>./Fire Emblem Echoes Shadows of Valentia (USA).cxi</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem Echoes: Shadows of Valentia</name>
		<desc>A tale of two armies with one destiny

In a continent that was torn asunder by warring gods, guide two armies through brutal tactical battlesâ€”as this reimagined RPG epic invades the West! Uncover the intertwining stories of Alm and Celica, engage foes, fend off dragons, and explore 3D dungeons. Your prowess will grow as you master this melding of modern and legacy Fire Emblemâ„¢ gameplay.

Alm and Celica lead separate armies united by a common goal: to stop the war and unify Valentia. Each army has its own path, units, and supplies, so balance their needs. Here, battle is waged in the traditions of elder Fire Emblemâ„¢ games, when the rules of battle were simpler, yet the challenge formidable as ever. When you encounter a dungeon, explore it in action-adventure style: smash false walls, break pots, or ambush enemies with a slash of your sword. You never know; you may stumble upon some uncommon itemsâ€¦or a hidden tactical battle with a brutal boss.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fire Emblem Echoes Shadows of Valentia (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Fire Emblem Echoes Shadows of Valentia (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fire Emblem Echoes Shadows of Valentia (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Fire Emblem Echoes Shadows of Valentia (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>33 =-  Fire Emblem Echoes Shadows of Valentia (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103714" />
	</game>
	<game id="10980">
		<path>./Pokemon Omega Ruby (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Pokemon Omega Ruby</name>
		<desc>In this enhanced remake of Pokémon Ruby Version, players travel throughout the Hoenn region on a journey to become a Pokémon Master. Like the original, the goal is to challenge the eight Pokémon Gyms of the Hoenn League and earn badges from their Gym Leaders, then take on the Elite Four and the Champion. However, the world is endangered when the villainous Team Magma tries to expand the continents by resurrecting the ancient Legendary Pokémon Groudon.

Aside from technical upgrades, the game is drastically changed in certain aspects. The Hoenn Pokédex is changed to add the evolutionary relatives of Pokémon from its original incarnation. Some Pokédex entries are also changed. Mega Evolution plays a major part of the storyline, and a new form change is introduced in the form of Primal Reversion, exclusive to Groudon and Kyogre. Some characters have had major redesigns in terms of appearance. Instead of roaming Hoenn after defeating the Champion as in the original, Latios automatically joins the player's party after summoning the player Southern Island. Latios can be used to soar through the skies of Hoenn, taking the player to locations known as Mirage Spots that cannot be reached otherwise. Pokémon Contests return under the name "Contest Spectacular" and have some new mechanics, while the basic format is largely the same.

After the main story, a new chapter called the Delta Episode is unlocked, allowing the player to once again save Hoenn from disaster. Finally, the Battle Tower is replaced by the Battle Resort, which features tough Trainers as well as a replica of the Battle Maison from Pokémon X and Y.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pokemon Omega Ruby (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Pokemon Omega Ruby (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pokemon Omega Ruby (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Pokemon Omega Ruby (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Pokémon</family>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>59 =-  Pokemon Omega Ruby (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103712" />
	</game>
	<game id="11072">
		<path>./Paper Mario - Sticker Star (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Paper Mario : Sticker Star</name>
		<desc>On the day of the annual Sticker Fest, Bowser decides to pull a prank and scatters six Royal Stickers across the land. To retrieve these mysterious, magical stickers, which are now stuck onto Bowser and his underlings, Mario sets off on an adventure with Kersti, a sticker fairy, visiting prairies, deserts, forests, snowy mountains and volcanoes around the world.</desc>
		<image>./images/Paper Mario - Sticker Star (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Paper Mario - Sticker Star (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Paper Mario - Sticker Star (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Paper Mario - Sticker Star (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20121111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>58 =-  Paper Mario - Sticker Star (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103720" />
	</game>
	<game id="154934">
		<path>./Pokemon Sun (USA).cxi</path>
		<name>Pokemon Sun</name>
		<desc>Pokémon Sun, along with Pokémon Moon, marks the start of the seventh generation of the Pokémon franchise. The game takes place in the Alola region, an archipelago whose culture, geography, and native wildlife are based on those of Hawaii. A number of Alola's native Pokémon have never been seen before, bringing the series' total number of Pokémon species to over 800.

The story follows a customizable protagonist who has just moved to the region and received their first Pokémon. What differs from past installments is that instead of the usual challenge of defeating eight Gyms, Alola is host to the island challenge, in which trainers face seven trials that test many other skills in addition to battling prowess. Only after clearing the seven trials and defeating the four island Kahunas can a trainer be called a champion. As the player character embarks on their island challenge, they are joined by a local boy named Hau, another newcomer to Alola named Lillie, and the mysterious Pokémon Cosmog that is under Lillie's protection. The group is forced to deal with Team Skull, a group of thugs who commit petty crimes under the leadership of their ruthless boss; the Aether Foundation, a wildlife conservation group with connections to Cosmog; and dangerous, otherworldly creatures called the Ultra Beasts.

As usual for a new pair of Pokémon games, Sun and Moon boast a number of new and improved features. HMs are now replaced by Ride Pokémon, which are unlocked over the course of the story and can be called upon at any time to provide transportation and clear obstacles. Hyper Training allows players to boost their Pokémon's individual values, hidden values that impact a Pokémon's potential for stat growth and are otherwise immutable. The new Battle Royal mode pits four trainers against each other in a free-for-all fight where the goal is to score the most KOs while trying not to let one's own Pokémon faint. A group of islands called Poké Pelago allow the player's Pokémon to play and collect items while they aren't in the active party, and each island can be upgraded to provide more and better rewards. Lastly, a location called the Festival Plaza acts as the multiplayer hub, and combines features from prior games' Join Avenue and PSS systems.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pokemon Sun (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Pokemon Sun (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pokemon Sun (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Pokemon Sun (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Pokémon</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>60 =-  Pokemon Sun (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103724" />
	</game>
	<game id="11209">
		<path>./Cars 2 (europe) (En,Fi,Sv,No,Da) Decrypted.3ds</path>
		<name>Cars 2</name>
		<desc>Inspired by the upcoming DisneyPixar animated film, Cars 2: The Video Game lets players jump into the Cars 2 universe with some of their favorite Cars personalities in exotic locations around the globe.</desc>
		<image>./images/Cars 2 (europe) (En,Fi,Sv,No,Da) Decrypted-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Cars 2 (europe) (En,Fi,Sv,No,Da) Decrypted-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cars 2 (europe) (En,Fi,Sv,No,Da) Decrypted-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Cars 2 (europe) (En,Fi,Sv,No,Da) Decrypted-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20111101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Firebrand Games</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Various</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>no,en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>10 =-  Cars 2 (europe) (En,Fi,Sv,No,Da) Decrypted</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103721" />
	</game>
	<game id="11183">
		<path>./Cave Story 3D (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Cave Story 3d</name>
		<desc>Having received tremendous acclaim in its previous releases on PC and WiiWare, Cave Story, an indie side scrolling 2D action game, now makes its way into an all new dimension with Cave Story 3D for Nintendo 3DS. At once both a throwback to classic 2D action platformers and also the potential future of the genre, Cave Story 3D blends tight controls, superb level design, and excellent story and presentation to deliver a memorable, addicting retro experience!</desc>
		<image>./images/Cave Story 3D (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Cave Story 3D (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cave Story 3D (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Cave Story 3D (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20111108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nicalis</developer>
		<publisher>Pixel</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>11 =-  Cave Story 3D (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103725" />
	</game>
	<game id="12074">
		<path>./Mario and Sonic at the Rio 2016 Olympic Games (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Sonic at the Rio 2016 Olympic Games</name>
		<desc>Compete On-the-go with Mario and Sonic! All of your favorite Mario? and Sonic characters are ready to join the fun in Rio de Janeiro, host of the Olympic Games in 2016. Then take the rivalry on the road with this portable collection of supercharged events like Soccer, Table Tennis, or test your skills in a challenging game of Golf. Take on fun and exciting events set throughout host city Rio de Janeiro. Join Mario, Sonic and your favorite characters to take on new challenging events like Soccer and Beach Volleyball. Soccer is a popular sport in Brazil where the Rio 2016 Olympic Games are set. Golf returns to the Olympic Games for the first time in 112 years; enjoy the event exclusively in the Nintendo 3DS version of Mario &amp; Sonic at the Rio 2016 Olympic Games.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mario and Sonic at the Rio 2016 Olympic Games (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Mario and Sonic at the Rio 2016 Olympic Games (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mario and Sonic at the Rio 2016 Olympic Games (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Mario and Sonic at the Rio 2016 Olympic Games (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20160408T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<family>Sonic</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>50 =-  Mario and Sonic at the Rio 2016 Olympic Games (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103728" />
	</game>
	<game id="11048">
		<path>./Mario Party - Island Tour (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Mario Party Island Tour</name>
		<desc>Mario Party: Island Tour lets you take the fun on the road with your Nintendo 3DS system!

Face off against friends and family in the all-new, ultimate Mario Party â€“ a portable minigame extravaganza thatâ€™s bursting with gameplay possibilities. If youâ€™ve never played a Mario Party game before, youâ€™re in for a treat.

Thereâ€™s always something new to see on the Party Islands.
In this ultimate showdown you can take on the road, blaze through the 7 new game boards, some of which take just minutes to play. Wrangle goombas and blast out of cannons as you tilt, tap, and draw through new minigames harnessing the unique functionality of Nintendo 3DS. Compete in new multiplayer modes including mind bending puzzles, minigame challenges, or enter a whole new reality with AR Card play for up to 4 players*. Whether in single or multiplayer, this is a portable party that never ends.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mario Party - Island Tour (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Mario Party - Island Tour (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mario Party - Island Tour (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Mario Party - Island Tour (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20131122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nd Cube</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>52 =-  Mario Party - Island Tour (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103732" />
	</game>
	<game id="12069">
		<path>./Dragon Quest VIII - Journey of the Cursed King (USA).cxi</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest VIII: Journey of the Cursed King</name>
		<desc>The court jester Dhoulmagus of the kingdom of Trodain stole a powerful magical scepter sealed beneath the royal castle. Using the power of the scepter, Dhoulmagus destroyed the castle, placed a curse upon the kingdom and its people, and turned King Trode into a troll and the princess into a horse. A sole surviving castle guard journeys with the king, the princess, a reformed bandit named Yangus and a few other companions in search of the evil jester and a way to break the curse. 

Dragon Quest VIII: Journey of the Cursed King is a traditional Japanese-style role-playing game with random enemy encounters, simple turn-based combat mechanics, and management of a party consisting of four characters, each belonging to a clearly defined class. Unlike its predecessors in the series and most Japanese RPGs in general, the game features a continuous world with fairly vast landscapes and integrated towns and dungeons, as opposed to world map traveling and locations represented by icons. The game features full camera rotation and optional first-person view. Like in the previous Dragon Quest games, many objects can be interacted with; for example, barrels can be physically lifted, carried, and broken, to reveal items hidden within.

In addition to experience points, the player receives skill points from battles, which can be manually allocated into a skill category of the player's choice. These categories include three different kinds of weapons, fisticuffs, and a discipline unique to each character. After a required amount of skill points has been invested into a particular category, the correspondent character learns a new ability or becomes more proficient with the chosen weapon. The Alchemy Pot system allows players to gather recipes and mix items to create new ones.

The international version of the game features several updates to the original Japanese version, including voice acting, graphic menu, symphonic soundtracks, and flashier effects.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dragon Quest VIII - Journey of the Cursed King (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Dragon Quest VIII - Journey of the Cursed King (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dragon Quest VIII - Journey of the Cursed King (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Dragon Quest VIII - Journey of the Cursed King (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>22 =-  Dragon Quest VIII - Journey of the Cursed King (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103734" />
	</game>
	<game id="11011">
		<path>./Luigis Mansion - Dark Moon (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Luigi's Mansion: Dark Moon</name>
		<desc>After the happenings of Luigi's Mansion, Luigi once again has to put on his ghostbusting gear. This time he visits Evershade Valley, where the destruction of the Dark Moon caused all ghosts to become hostile to humans. Luigi is hired by the eccentric professor Gadd to visit five haunted mansions to retrieve the Dark Moon parts.

Luigi's weapon of choice is vacuum device called PolterGust 5000 which is used to fight against the numerous ghost enemies. The basic procedure is always the same: Luigi has to stun the ghosts with the flashlight (in contrast to the predecessor, now the position and angle is important) so he can vacuum them in. Of course the ghosts struggle against it, so their movement has to be countered with the analogue stick. There are different kinds of enemies which require a variation of tactics, e.g. some ghosts have sunglasses which have to be removed first and others are only vulnerable briefly. There are also multi-stage bossfights. 

The PolterGust 5000 is also used to solve puzzles, for example by sucking in a stove and using the flames to ignite something else. It is also a good idea to use the vacuum device on physical objects in the mansions in order to find secret passages or treasure. When Luigi picks up enough treasure, the PolterGust 5000 is automatically upgraded.

Besides the campaign, there is also a multiplayer mode which takes place in the ScareScraper, mansion with 25 floors. The available modes are hunter (sucking in as many ghosts as possible in a limited amount of time), rush (finding the exit in a limited amount of time; clocks can be picked up to extend the time limit) and polterpup (tracking down polterpulps, invisible ghosts, with the flashlight).</desc>
		<image>./images/Luigis Mansion - Dark Moon (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Luigis Mansion - Dark Moon (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Luigis Mansion - Dark Moon (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Luigis Mansion - Dark Moon (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20130101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Next Level Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>46 =-  Luigis Mansion - Dark Moon (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103737" />
	</game>
	<game id="11690">
		<path>./Culdcept Revolt (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Culdcept</name>
		<desc>Culdcept is a hybrid board/card game where the objective is to generate the most mana before making it back to the castle.

Each player starts out with a deck of 50 cards. Card types range from monster cards (e.g. Skeleton), which are used to accumulate territory on the board to increase your mana; Equipment (e.g. Chain Mail), which will boost your monsters' abilities when they battle; and Magic (e.g. Holy Word 0), which can be used to help you or hinder the other players on the board. When a player lands on another player's monster, he/she can challenge it to a battle in an attempt to take over the territory. If the attacker wins, he/she gets the space on the board and additional mana.

There are more than sixteen different game boards, each with different rules and layouts (such as the maximum number on dice rolls, the elements on the board, etc.)</desc>
		<image>./images/Culdcept Revolt (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Culdcept Revolt (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Culdcept Revolt (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Culdcept Revolt (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<releasedate>20120628T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>OmiyaSoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>17 =-  Culdcept Revolt (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103739" />
	</game>
	<game id="11392">
		<path>./Pac-Man &amp; Galaga Dimensions (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Pac-Man &amp; Galaga Dimensions</name>
		<desc>PAC-MAN and Galaga bring their iconic gameplay to spectacular 3D in an exciting six game package for the Nintendo 3DS! Enjoy classic hits PAC-MAN, PAC-MAN Championship Edition, Galaga, and Galaga Legions, or play two brand new games developed exclusively for the Nintendo 3DS. In PAC-MAN Tilt, move PAC-MAN through stages filled with obstacles, platforms and ghosts with tilt controls. Flippers, platforms and power pellets help PAC-MAN jump, flip, swing, and eat his way to the finish line. Rid space of the incoming Galaga army by shooting down enemies in an exciting 3D skirmish in Galaga 3D Impact!</desc>
		<image>./images/Pac-Man &amp; Galaga Dimensions (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Pac-Man &amp; Galaga Dimensions (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pac-Man &amp; Galaga Dimensions (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Pac-Man &amp; Galaga Dimensions (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20110826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Various</genre>
		<family>Pac-Man</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>57 =-  Pac-Man &amp; Galaga Dimensions (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103741" />
	</game>
	<game id="11683">
		<path>./LBX Little Battlers eXperience (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>LBX: Little Battlers eXperience</name>
		<desc>Collect, build and battle your palm-sized robot. Play as Van Yamano, a young boy who comes upon a unique LBX - a complex, customizable, palm-sized robot. Use it - and team up with familiar characters from the hit TV series - to take down the evil corporation known as the New Dawn Raisers.

Features:
-Collect and build your own palm-sized robot from more than 4,000 parts to create a one-of-a-kind LBX
-Choose from more than 130 different complete sets of matching parts, or mix and match.
-Customize both external parts and interior parts individually to enhance your LBXs capabilities.
-Battle as your LBX against friends and foes in third-person view with local wireless multiplayer mode.
-Battle other LBX models in 20 different arenas with unique environmental characteristics.
-In local wireless multiplayer play, up to six players can battle using a variety of different rules</desc>
		<image>./images/LBX Little Battlers eXperience (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/LBX Little Battlers eXperience (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/LBX Little Battlers eXperience (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/LBX Little Battlers eXperience (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20120705T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Level-5</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>40 =-  LBX Little Battlers eXperience (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103751" />
	</game>
	<game id="12082">
		<path>./Hyrule Warriors Legends (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Hyrule Warriors Legends</name>
		<desc>Cut down entire legions of enemies as fan-favorite Legend of Zelda characters using powerful moves as Hyrule Warriors comes to the Nintendo 3DS. Control multiple characters to enhance your strategies and enjoy new story elements with playable characters from The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker, such as Tetra, King Daphnes, and more.

War rages as the delicate balance of the Triforce is disrupted. The kingdom of Hyrule is once again being torn apart by a dark power, this time lead by Sorceress Cia. Now it's up to the legendary hero Link to face hordes of enemies and find the missing Princess Zelda. Advance the story to unlock new playable characters, each with unique moves and weapon types. Collect Rupees and other useful items to upgrade weapons and craft badges, which you can use to bolster each warrior's abilities.</desc>
		<image>./images/Hyrule Warriors Legends (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Hyrule Warriors Legends (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hyrule Warriors Legends (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Hyrule Warriors Legends (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<developer>Omega Force</developer>
		<publisher>Koei</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>37 =-  Hyrule Warriors Legends (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103749" />
	</game>
	<game id="11251">
		<path>./Bella Sara - The Magical Horse Adventures (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Bella Sara : The Magical Horse Adventures</name>
		<image>./images/Bella Sara - The Magical Horse Adventures (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Bella Sara - The Magical Horse Adventures (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bella Sara - The Magical Horse Adventures (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Bella Sara - The Magical Horse Adventures (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<developer>Bigben Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Eko Software</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>836aab163ed3905bdd5fed705e0384a9</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>07 =-  Bella Sara - The Magical Horse Adventures (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103743" />
	</game>
	<game id="176005">
		<path>./Alliance Alive, The (USA).cxi</path>
		<name>The Alliance Alive</name>
		<desc>The makers of The Legend of Legacy bring the classic JRPG back to form in The Alliance Alive, a new adventure that evokes the nostalgia of the JRPG greats by offering huge world-exploration, an intertwining story of 9 protagonists, and well-designed battle mechanics.


One thousand years ago, Daemons invaded the world of Humans. They subjugated Humanity and created the Great Barrier to separate the realms. The world was thrown into upheaval, and the Dark Current was born. Humanity was decimated and now Daemons rule atop a hierarchical society. However, the time for resistance has come. The world is about to change yet again...


A World Like No Other


Built on a sprawling world brimming with numerous secrets to discover,players will need to establish and unite guilds throughout the four realms while battling the Daemons.


Engage in Unique Combat


Use the "Ignition" system, a part of the turn-based combat that allows 
for deep customization and nuanced gameplay, to reach an enhanced state 
and deliver devastating Final Strikes.</desc>
		<image>./images/Alliance Alive, The (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Alliance Alive, The (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Alliance Alive, The (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Alliance Alive, The (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<developer>Cattle Call, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>04 =-  Alliance Alive, The (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103746" />
	</game>
	<game id="11396">
		<path>./Dream Trigger 3D (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Dream Trigger 3d</name>
		<desc>Dream Trigger 3D showcases the wow factor of the 3DS like no other game. A stunning mixture of explosive graphics and nonstop action, it is a signature shooter for the system. Play as a fixer of dreams', turning nightmare landscapes into gorgeous dreamscapes in this must-have visual masterpiece for new 3DS owners.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dream Trigger 3D (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Dream Trigger 3D (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dream Trigger 3D (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Dream Trigger 3D (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20110610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Art Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>23 =-  Dream Trigger 3D (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103754" />
	</game>
	<game id="11151">
		<path>./Metroid - Samus Returns (USA).cxi</path>
		<name>Metroid : Samus Returns</name>
		<desc>Metroid: Samus Returns is a side-scrolling action-adventure video game developed collaboratively by MercurySteam and Nintendo, with the latter also publishing it for the Nintendo 3DS handheld game console. A part of the science fiction Metroid series, the game is a reimagining of the 1991 Game Boy game Metroid II: Return of Samus, and was released worldwide on 15 September 2017. It follows series protagonist Samus Aran, who is sent by the Galactic Federation to exterminate the parasitic Metroids on their home planet of SR388.
The game features a story and structure similar to Metroid II but with new controls, visuals, and gameplay. It also introduces some features that are new to the 2D Metroid games, such as melee counterattacks, an ability to fire freely at any angle, and a selection of different abilities. The development on Samus Returns began in 2015, with longtime Metroid developer Yoshio Sakamoto producing it. The game was met with positive reception from video game journalists, who praised its visuals and improved gameplay over the original game, with many viewing it as a return to form for the series.</desc>
		<image>./images/Metroid - Samus Returns (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Metroid - Samus Returns (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Metroid - Samus Returns (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Metroid - Samus Returns (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20170915T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>53 =-  Metroid - Samus Returns (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103754" />
	</game>
	<game id="11087">
		<path>./Etrian Odyssey 2 Untold - The Fafnir Knight (Europe) Decrypted.3ds</path>
		<name>Etrian Odyssey 2 Untold: The Fafnir Knight</name>
		<desc>Etrian Odyssey 2 Untold - The Fafnir Knight is a continuation of the Untold spin-off series for Etrian Odyssey. This Etrian Odyssey Untold game is an upgraded and enhanced version of the original Nintendo DS game: Etrian Odyssey II: Heroes of Lagaard.

In the same line as Etrian Odyssey Untold: The Millennium Girl, this Untold game features an enhanced version of the original Nintendo DS game, which one can play through in the "Classic Mode" or can explore the mystery of the Fafnir Knight (the so-called "Untold" part) in the "Story Mode".

 Classic Mode: Customizable characters and maps, with a slight different plot compared to the new "Story Mode"

 Story Mode: Standard characters, broad and widened background stories, cutscenes &amp; voiceacting

There are three difficulty settings possible when starting a new game: Picnic, Normal &amp; Expert. Data is transferrable from the Classic Mode to the new Story Mode.</desc>
		<image>./images/Etrian Odyssey 2 Untold - The Fafnir Knight (Europe) Decrypted-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Etrian Odyssey 2 Untold - The Fafnir Knight (Europe) Decrypted-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Etrian Odyssey 2 Untold - The Fafnir Knight (Europe) Decrypted-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Etrian Odyssey 2 Untold - The Fafnir Knight (Europe) Decrypted-image.png</mix>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>24 =-  Etrian Odyssey 2 Untold - The Fafnir Knight (Europe) Decrypted</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103757" />
	</game>
	<game id="11545">
		<path>./3D Game Collection (USA).cxi</path>
		<name>3d Game Collection</name>
		<desc>It's finally here: The first games collection for Nintendo 3DS in eShop!
    
      It's finally here: The first games collection for Nintendo 3DS in eShop!
    
      
      Play a round of Sudoku, do a relaxing puzzle or make the other player's 
      ships sink to the bottom of the sea. A grand total of 25 game types in 
      three magnificently themed worlds provide plenty of variety and lots of 
      fun.
    

    
      Accept the challenge and try to collect all the trophies. But be warned 
      - it won't be easy! Every game learns and adapts to your abilities!
    
    
      These are the game types:
    
    
      4 in a rowBackgammonBingoCard SolitaireCheckersChest 
      Mover ManiaChinese CheckersCode CrackerDice FiveDominoFind 
      MinesFind PairsJigsaw PuzzleKakuroLudoMahJonggMatch 
      3Nine Men's MorrisPeg SolitairePipe ShiftShip EncounterSliding 
      PuzzleSpot the DifferenceSudokuToken Wangle
    
    
      The first games collection for Nintendo 3DS in eShop!
    
    
      55 x fun for the entire family!
    
    
      Round up all the available trophies
    
    
      to be declared the winner!</desc>
		<image>./images/3D Game Collection (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/3D Game Collection (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/3D Game Collection (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/3D Game Collection (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<developer>Reactor s.c.</developer>
		<publisher>Joindots</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220218T092417</lastplayed>
		<md5>e4d963de24071ba082a57168a40c2cbe</md5>
		<gametime>13</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>01 =-  3D Game Collection (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103752" />
	</game>
	<game id="176337">
		<path>./Pokemon Super Mystery Dungeon (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Pokemon Super Mystery Dungeon</name>
		<desc>The definitive Pokemon Mystery Dungeon! Prepare yourself for a grand adventure where you become a Pokemon and battle alongside Legendary and Mythical Pokemon to help save the world! Befriend Pokemon and explore ever-changing mystery dungeons with them! Players are suddenly transformed into a Pokemon and sent out to a world inhabited only by Pokemon. From a group of 20 Pokemon, including the starters from core RPG Pokemon games plus Pikachu and Riolu, you can choose your Pokemon and your partner Pokemon! Battle alongside your partner Pokemon, who will become your best friend as you investigate ever-changing dungeons. Befriend and interact with all 720 known Pokemon as you attempt to save the world from a crisis in a tale of unprecedented scale! The possibilities are limitless!</desc>
		<image>./images/Pokemon Super Mystery Dungeon (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Pokemon Super Mystery Dungeon (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pokemon Super Mystery Dungeon (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Pokemon Super Mystery Dungeon (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<releasedate>20160219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The pokemon company LTD.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Pokémon</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>61 =-  Pokemon Super Mystery Dungeon (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103804" />
	</game>
	<game id="176088">
		<path>./Dragon Ball - Fusions (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Dragon Ball Fusions</name>
		<desc>Dragon Ball Fusions is an RPG action game that combines fighting, customization, and collection elements to bring Dragon Ball to the next level. In this new world, players will discover powerful items, find warriors who can become their allies, and build teams to bring into battle to see who the best fighters are. The battle system combines strategy and real time action to make this a fun and unique Dragon Ball experience for fans.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dragon Ball - Fusions (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Dragon Ball - Fusions (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dragon Ball - Fusions (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Dragon Ball - Fusions (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<developer>Ganbarion Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>20 =-  Dragon Ball - Fusions (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103806" />
	</game>
	<game id="176215">
		<path>./Legends of Oz - Dorothy's Return (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Legends of Oz - Dorothy's Return</name>
		<desc>Dorothy is Back!
Oz is in Trouble again thanks to the evil Jester! A new villain named Jester showed up on the scene and started kidnapping a lot of the legends of Oz! Scarecrow, Lion and the Tin Man were all captured by his flying monkeys, and now theyre being held with others against their will! Dorothy needs to recruit some new companions to help her make it to the Emerald City. With exciting new lands of Oz to explore, you can help Dorothy and become a Legend of Oz!</desc>
		<image>./images/Legends of Oz - Dorothy's Return (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Legends of Oz - Dorothy's Return (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Legends of Oz - Dorothy's Return (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Legends of Oz - Dorothy's Return (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>600202e6ad4374014deb7e2a2b1ec38f</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>44 =-  Legends of Oz - Dorothy's Return (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103810" />
	</game>
	<game id="11380">
		<path>./Crash Time 3D (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Crash Time 3d</name>
		<image>./images/Crash Time 3D (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Crash Time 3D (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Crash Time 3D (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Crash Time 3D (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<developer>DTP Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Synetic</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<md5>e6516f6b3e8e2312c7e841b0cbf62d7f</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>15 =-  Crash Time 3D (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103807" />
	</game>
	<game id="10987">
		<path>./Animal Crossing - New Leaf (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Animal Crossing - New Leaf</name>
		<desc>Animal Crossing: New Leaf is a social simulation game. You take on the role as the new mayor in a small village populated by animals. Game play consists of improving the village with new buildings and decorations, collecting furniture and items for your own house as well as donating fossils, fish, insects and art to the local museum.

There's more to discover than ever before in the Animal Crossingâ„¢: New Leafâ€”Welcome amiibo game! This updated version of Animal Crossingâ„¢: New Leaf adds in support for all Animal Crossing series amiibo figures and cards.</desc>
		<image>./images/Animal Crossing - New Leaf (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Animal Crossing - New Leaf (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Animal Crossing - New Leaf (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Animal Crossing - New Leaf (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>08/11/2012</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<family>Animal Crossing</family>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount />
		<lastplayed />
		<gametime />
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>06 =-  Animal Crossing - New Leaf (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103738" />
	</game>
	<game id="10996">
		<path>./Fire Emblem - Awakening (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem: Awakening</name>
		<desc>Fire Emblem Awakening offers a unique blend of in-battle strategy, vast character customization, and lush 3D cinematic graphics that appeal to a wide range of gamers. In this game, you'll join Chrom, brother to Ylisse's empress and commander of its forces, in a fantasy world teetering on the brink of war. It's your duty to guide a team of Ylisse's finest soldiers--knights, mages, archers, and more--against the marauding Plegian bandits. To succeed, you will need to carefully choose the units you take into battle. As you lead your team through battles across maps that span entire kingdoms, your army will grow. Some characters are willing to join you quickly, while others may need more persuasion. Each character earns experience in battle, leveling up and gaining strength and abilities as they do so. It's up to you to guide their moves, choose their weapons, and direct their attacks.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fire Emblem - Awakening (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Fire Emblem - Awakening (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fire Emblem - Awakening (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Fire Emblem - Awakening (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>04/02/2013</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Intelligent Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount />
		<lastplayed />
		<gametime />
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>31 =-  Fire Emblem - Awakening (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103741" />
	</game>
	<game id="10997">
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - A Link Between Worlds (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - A Link Between Worlds</name>
		<desc>Two worlds collide in an all-new adventure set in the world of Super NES classic The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past. In this newly spun tale, Link transforms into a living painting to cross into a dark, parallel dimension mirroring Hyrule. Conquer the puzzles, traps, and hidden rooms of deadly dungeons to save both worlds from certain doom! 

Brought to life in 3D, this beloved, top-down world is the perfect backdrop for a sweeping new tale. Dungeons sink deep below the screen as Link and his attacks pop out, highlighting the nonstop action. The pace is faster than ever, especially since you can swap items on the Nintendo 3DS touch screen. Shoot an arrow, toss a boomerang, bomb a wall, then merge into a painting to slide between two worlds - all in a matter of seconds. With gameplay, visuals, and controls this smooth and consistent, no Zelda adventure has ever been so action-packed.</desc>
		<image>./images/Legend of Zelda, The - A Link Between Worlds (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Legend of Zelda, The - A Link Between Worlds (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Legend of Zelda, The - A Link Between Worlds (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Legend of Zelda, The - A Link Between Worlds (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>22/11/2013</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>The Legend of Zelda</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount />
		<lastplayed />
		<gametime />
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>42 =-  Legend of Zelda, The - A Link Between Worlds (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103637" />
	</game>
	<game id="11000">
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time 3D (Europe).3ds</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - Ocarina of Time 3D</name>
		<desc>The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time 3D brings a completely re-mastered version of an epic entry in the beloved The Legend of Zelda game series to Nintendos newest hand-held system, Nintendo 3DS. The game couples phenomenally enhanced graphics with stunning, glasses-free 3D visuals to bring to life the daring adventures of its hero, Link. A streamlined touch-screen interface and newly implemented motion controls provide a fresh and intuitive feel as players immerse themselves in the tale of the creation of Hyrule and the struggle for control of its all-powerful ancient relic. The game will also feature new challenges not included in the original game. The Legend of Zelda veterans can look forward to the Master Quest a second quest with revamped puzzles and redesigned dungeons that feature the same graphical and interface upgrades as the main game. The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time 3D is a masterful improvement on one of the landmark releases in video game history.</desc>
		<image>./images/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time 3D (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time 3D (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time 3D (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time 3D (Europe)-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19/06/2011</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Grezzo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>The Legend of Zelda</family>
		<playcount />
		<lastplayed />
		<gametime />
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<sortname>43 =-  Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time 3D (Europe)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103613" />
	</game>
	<game id="10990">
		<path>./Monster.Hunter.4.Ultimate.3ds</path>
		<name>Monster Hunter 4 Ultimate</name>
		<desc>Monster Hunter 4 Ultimate (called Monster Hunter 4G in Japan) is the newest installment in the popular Monster Hunter series, which has sold more than 28 million units worldwide to date. In Monster Hunter 4 Ultimate, players will take on the role of a hunter that joins up with a traveling caravan to explore new lands and towns along the way. This grand adventure will include hundreds of quests to take on a variety of extraordinary creatures that yield valuable resources used for weapons and equipment. Launching on Nintendo 3DS, Monster Hunter 4 Ultimate represents the biggest leap forward ever for the series with more new content and exciting features than ever before. Also, for the first time ever for the Monster Hunter series on a handheld system, players will be able to join up with friends over the internet via the Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection, as well as the previously available local wireless option.</desc>
		<image>./images/Monster.Hunter.4.Ultimate-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Monster.Hunter.4.Ultimate-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Monster.Hunter.4.Ultimate-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Monster.Hunter.4.Ultimate-image.png</mix>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>11/10/2014</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
		<playcount />
		<lastplayed />
		<gametime />
		<lang>en</lang>
		<sortname>56 =-  Monster.Hunter.4.Ultimate</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103631" />
	</game>
	<game id="176105">
		<path>./Fire Emblem - Fates Birthright (USA).3ds</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem Fates: Birthright</name>
		<desc>A youth has grown up as one of the royal children of the glory-seeking nation of Nohr. Though their father has forbidden them to leave the castle, they still live a happy life with their four siblings. However, when they finally are sent to the outside world, it is on a mission to Hoshido, a peace-loving country that Nohr has plans to invade. There they learn that they were born to the Hoshido royal family, and were kidnapped by Nohr as an infant. A Nohr princess named Azura was taken hostage by Hoshido in retaliation, and has been living in a similar situation to the protagonist. With war looming on the horizon, Azura and the protagonist choose to side with their family in Hoshido, and defend it against the invading Nohr forces.

Birthright is one of three versions of Fire Emblem Fates, the others being Conquest and Revelation. In this version, the player controls their fully customizable avatar as they lead Hoshido's forces in strategic battles against Nohr-allied enemies. Gameplay is similar to Fire Emblem Awakening, with less challenging gameplay and the opportunity to grind for money, items, and experience in between storyline battles. In addition to the Classic and Casual modes featured in Awakening, this game contains Phoenix Mode, in which defeated allies are immediately resurrected on the following turn. Players pick one of these three modes at the start of the game, but may choose to permanently switch from Classic or Casual to a less difficult mode later on.

Supports also return from Awakening, allowing characters to build their relationships as they fight alongside each other. Two characters of the opposite sex may get married and have children once their relationship has progressed enough, and Birthright also includes the possibility of a same-sex relationship if the player chooses the female protagonist.

A feature called My Castle allows the player to build and customize a village that can contain various helpful buildings, such as shops that sell weapons or healing items. The village can be upgraded with resources collected through StreetPass, and it is also where StreetPass battles are held. Winning a StreetPass battle allows the player to recruit one of the defeated opponent units into their own army, and a shop in the village allows players to purchase other special units called Einherjard.

Players may purchase DLC that allows them to play through the Conquest and Revelation scenarios as well.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fire Emblem - Fates Birthright (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Fire Emblem - Fates Birthright (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fire Emblem - Fates Birthright (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<mix>./images/Fire Emblem - Fates Birthright (USA)-image.png</mix>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20240313T173155</lastplayed>
		<gametime>16</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<sortname>32 =-  Fire Emblem - Fates Birthright (USA)</sortname>
		<genreid>0</genreid>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220219T103636" />
	</game>
</gameList>